<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://mdaku.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:52:34 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mdaku.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Waiting On First Submissions</title>
      <link>https://mdaku.github.io/posts/waiting-first-submissions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:52:34 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mdaku.github.io/posts/waiting-first-submissions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time coming. I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing forever, but never bothered&#xA;to submit anything anywhere.  I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what changed, but something snapped&#xA;and now I&amp;rsquo;m all in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m currently waiting on five submissions. I&amp;rsquo;ll post here after decisions are&#xA;made and I have something to share.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a strange feeling that I don&amp;rsquo;t really care if these pieces are rejected or not,&#xA;the one thing I learned in academia was that it&amp;rsquo;s rarely the case that something shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be published, it&amp;rsquo;s really just a question of fit.  So I am focusing on trying to find the right home for these pieces while at the same time consistently producing more.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mdaku.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mdaku.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mark Daku is a Canadian writer living in Greece.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A former academic and UN worker, he has recently returned to writing. His work delves into themes of loneliness, isolation, existentialism, and grief, particularly in the context of hyper-mobility and nomadic lifestyle choices. He explores these themes primarily through creative non-fiction and speculative fiction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently, he lives in Athens, Greece.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mdaku.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mdaku.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am on Bluesky &lt;a href=&#34;https://bsky.app/profile/markdaku.bsky.social&#34;&gt;@markdaku.bsky.social&lt;/a&gt; and you can e-mail me &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hibachi-crow79@icloud.com&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://mdaku.github.io/writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mdaku.github.io/writing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creative Non-Fiction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Warning Labels (under review): An exploration of grief in the wake of loss&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One In, One Out (under review): A love letter to reading and physical books&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ærøskøbing (work-in-progress): A couple struggles to get married in the midst of the pandemic before an international move&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Short Fiction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Static of the Universe (under review): An astronaut orbits the moon, reeling from the loss of her crewmates in a lunar lander crash. Struggling with grief and isolation, she is confronted with the possibility of the Earth’s disappearance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Carry On, Gregory (under review): Gregory lives out of his suitcase, traveling the world until he finds it impossible to stop.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Even I Will One Day Cease (under review): A man awakens on a ship, drifting in space, alone. A chance encounter with something beautiful transforms him.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Peer-Reviewed Academic Book Chapters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
